ILGWU Organizing Department Records 5780/144
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Organizing Department Records
1961-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Organizing Dept
5780/144
13 cubic feet
13 linear ft.
Records (dcuments).
The collection contains correspondence, memoranda, reports, and printed material created or collected by the Organizing and Field Services Department.
5510314
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
C. Berne, August 11, 2009
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
The ILGWU established the Department of Organization and Field Services in 1980. The department was responsible for, among other things, the coordination and survey of organizing activities, coordination and administration of information services including computer utilization, and the administration of all OSHA-related matters. It also coordinated the identification and implementation of new services.
As the ILGWU's central office for organizing, the Department of Organization and Field Services worked with affiliates of the international (e.g., local unions, district councils, and regional departments) in dealing with issues in their locations. In addition to working with union affiliates, the department also worked on legal and legislative fronts to ensure safe conditions for garment workers. Insofar as the department conducted surveys and gathered information, its work resembled that of the Research Department, and insofar as it supported pro-labor legislative efforts. To make clear the primary purpose of the Department of Organization and Field Services, the Report and Proceedings from the 1983 ILGWU Convention noted that, "The central concern is organization, and from this has stemmed the other broad activities which require skills, knowledge and information to be successful."
Scope and Contents
Taken together, the two collections comprising the records of the Department of Organization and Field Services provide a general sense of the work of the department, though they are not physically extensive. Organizing efforts by affiliate organizations of the ILGWU, and on which department staff assisted, may be documented in that affiliate's records or elsewhere in the ILGWU records.
Arranged alphabetically, these records (5780/144) include correspondence, memoranda, reports, printed material created or collected by the Organizing and Field Services Department, and other material relating to its activities dating from between 1961 and 1989. In addition to documenting routine operations of the department, these records also include documentation of efforts to roll back imports, including reports on congressional visits on a resolution on the subject. Also included are monthly reports on organizing activities from joint boards and regional departments, as well as periodic reports submitted by local unions', joint boards', and regional departments' organizing departments to the central organizing department; these reports include names of organizers and shops organized, and descriptions of current, future, and abandoned campaigns that were to be included in the Organizing Department's reports to the General Executive Board.
The ILGWU's company files (5780/205) contain Dun and Bradstreet Report on companies, reports on the companies' activities with non-ILGWU firms, memoranda on companies and efforts to organize workers therein, as well as some authorization cards.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/205: ILGWU Company Files
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Organizing Dept
5510314
- Abiline Christine University, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abrams, Robert - Attorney General, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Acevedo, Luis A., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Advance Staff Training Institute, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Advanced Organizers Program, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Advanced Staff Training Institute, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Affiliates Weekly Reports, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Survey, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Airlie Foundation, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- American Association of University Professors (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Apparel Imports, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Appleton, Shelly - General Secretary Treasurer, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Association of Flight Attendants, AFL-CIO, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Attitudes Surveys, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Audit Percentages (U-NU) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Barbero Hearing, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Barbero, Frank - Assemblyman, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Barbero, Frank - New York Assembly, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Benefit Fund/Theodore Bernstein, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bermudez, Melvin, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Bills, Vouchers, and Payments, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Boycott Letter, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Brooklyn Wage and Hour Office, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Budget, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Scope and Contents
  ILGWU Montreal
- Bureau of National Affairs, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bye, Arnold, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Campaign Committee, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Carrier Travel, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Catholic Migration Office, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Census, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Central States, 1982-1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Certificate of Appreciation (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Chaikin and Chaikin Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Chaikin, Sol C. - President, 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Clerical Workers/Women in the Workforce, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- COHOPS Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Computer Softwear, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Congress - Facts, Directory, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Congressional Visits, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Contrato de Amor (Box 1, Folder 40)
  In Spanish
- Convention, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Convention, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Convention Report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  January
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  February
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  March
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  April
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  May
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  July
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  August
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  September
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  October
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  November
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  December
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  June
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Cottage Connection, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- CWA Strike, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Daniels, Wilbur - Executive Vice President, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Department of Labor, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Developing New Tactics: Winning with Coordinated Corporate Campaigns, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Directory of National Unions and Employee Associations, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Distribution of Leaflets (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Eastern Pennsylvania, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Elections - National Labor Relations Board, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Elections - National Labor Relations Board (History), 1961-1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Employment, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Employment, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Enterprise Zone Legislation and Hearings, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Evaluation Forms, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Evolution in the Workplace" AFL-CIO, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Evolution of Work Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Experienced Organizer Institute, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Fashion Models (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Faux, Mary, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Finance Department, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Fire Department, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Frontlash, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Future of Organizing - Unity House, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Garment Industry Advisory Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- General Advisory Council, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  August 19-21
- General Executive Board, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- General Executive Board - Organization Department Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- General Executive Board - Organizing Directors' Reports, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board Committee on Organization, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- General Executive Board Department of Organization and Field Services, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- General Executive Board Organization Department Reports, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- General Executive Board Organization Department Reports, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Organization Task Force, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Report, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board Report - Department of Organization and Field Services, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board Report - Department of Organization and Field Services, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board Report - Task Force on Organization and New Directions, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board Reports, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board Reports - Department of Organization and Field Service, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board Reports and Correspondence, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board Subcommittee on Staff Development, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board Task Force on Organization and New Directions, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1982-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies Catalog, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies Catalog, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Giardina, Sal New York State District, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Gordon, Sonia, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Gross, Stanley Scranton District Council, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Guide to Basic Law and Procedures under the National Labor Relations Act, A, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Haupert, Joanne, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Hawaii Garment Industry, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Hazentown Agreement, 1979-1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Hazentown Agreement, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Health and Safety Department, ILGWU, 1981-1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Health and Safety Department, ILGWU, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Henry T. White Correspondence, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Hermanson, Jeff, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Hi-Tech Industries, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Hi-Tech Project, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Homework and Sweatshop Basic Information, 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Homework Regulation, 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Horror Stories, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- ILGWU - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- ILGWU Forms (Box 5, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Forms (Box 5, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Union News (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Immigration, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  In English and Spanish
- Immigration, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Immigration, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Immigration Task Force, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Import Campaign, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Import Clauses, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Import Leaflet Distribution List, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Import Leaflets Distributions Lists (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Import Penetration in the Apparel Industry, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Imports, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Imports, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Imports, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Imports, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Incoming Correspondence, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Incoming Correspondence, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Inside Game: Winning with Workplace Strategies, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Insurance, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Invoices and Orders, 1982-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- It's Your Union: A Steward's Guide to Effective Representation (Box 5, Folder 22)
- IUD Survey, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Labor Day Parade, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Labor Day Parade, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Leaflets (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Les Retrouvailles, New York-Quebec, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Letters to Senators Recommending Raymond G. Cordelli, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Lobbying Albany 3603-A/163-A, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Local 23-25, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Marcus, Hilary, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Master Agreements - Wilbur Daniels, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Mayo, Jerome, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Mazur, Jay - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Mazur, Jay - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Media Reports, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Media Reports, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Metro City Organizers, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Monthly Organization Activity Reports from Affiliates, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Monthly Update Reports, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Monthly Update Reports, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Montreal Region, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Montreal Region, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- NCO Requests - NYC Office, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Nemaizer, Samuel - Dress Joint Board, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- New Jersey Homework and Sweatshop Legislation, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- New York City Organization Seminar, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- New York City Organizers Conference, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- New York State AFL-CIO, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Newspaper and Media Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Newspaper Articles/Clippings, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Ogden, Allison, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Organization Conference Central States, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Organization Department Meeting Notes, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Organization Directors, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Organization Directors Meeting, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Organization Directors Meeting, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Organization Directors Meeting - Unity House, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Organization Directors Meeting - Unity House, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Outgoing Correspondence, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Payroll Change Advice, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Payroll Change Advice, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania State University Seminar, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Peretsman, Miriam, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Personnel, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Phillips Center for Public Research - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Phillips Center for Public Research - Vouchers, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Publicity and Press Releases, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Publicity Guide (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Quebec Joint Council, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Queens College Center, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Queens Community College, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Queens Taskforce, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Register of Reporting Labor Organizations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Registered Apparel Manufacturers, Freedom of Information Law, New York State, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Report for the Union Health Center Committee of the General Executive Board, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Report on Union Busters, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Report to the Governor and Legislature on Garment Manufacturing, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Resolutions Passed, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Resolutions/Congressional Representatives, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Responses - Congressional Visits, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Responses - Congressional Visits, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Road to Dignity, The" AFL-CIO, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Roth, Lee, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Sample Presentation to Congress (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Sites, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Solidarity 111/Imports, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Solidarity 111/Labor Day, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Southeast Region, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Southeast Region, 1979-1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Southeast Region, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Spillett, Leslie West - Canadian Region, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Staff Information (Sample Letters, Speeches), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Statement of ILGWU in Opposition to the Removal of Restrictions on Industrial Homework, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  1-Jul
- Steers, Tom - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Strikes, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Strongin, Paul - Southern California District Council, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Study on Industrial Homework, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Sympathy and Get Well Cards (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Synopsis of the 1988 Gallup Study of Public Knowledge and Opinion Concerning the Labor Movement (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Tele Concepts Contract, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Tele Concepts Correspondence, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Tele Concepts Correspondence, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Tele Concepts in Communications, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Teleconference Evaluations, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Temporary Office Personnel, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Testimony - Siems, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Training Institute, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Trimmings, Accessories, and Fabrics Expo Show Directory, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  November 3-5
- U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission - Fred Alvarez, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- U.S.X. Steel Workers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Undocumented Workers (Organizing and Representing), 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Union News, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Union White Paper - "Trouble on Fashion Avenue", 1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Upper South Department, 1980-1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Uzzle, Gail, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Ventura, Mario, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Video Conference Sites, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Volunteer Organizers, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Wages: Union/Non-Union, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Waldinger, Roger, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Walker, Carl, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Walkie Talkies Check Out Sheets, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Wall, Cornelius - Western States, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Welfare Fund Drafts, Document Number 7, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- West Canadian Region District Council, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Wilson, Rand, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Withdrawal from Association by Firm, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Word Star, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Word Star, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Youngdahl, James - Attorney, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Zimny, Max - Legal Counsel, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Zinn, Harris - Sportswear Joint Board, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- D'Ambrosio Textile Reprocessing Company, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Decorative Aides Company, INC., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Domsey International Sales Corporation, company leaflets, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Durlacher Company, 1987-1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Eastland Woodland Mills, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Friedman Leather Fashions, 1986-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Goodwill Industries of America, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Henry Lee, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- GAP, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- GAP, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Hampshire Group, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Hanna Anderson Corporation, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Homegoods, INC., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Jenna Couture, INC., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Jessica McClintock, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- John Kiss and Sons, INC., 1982-1995 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- JoJu Textiles, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Jordache (U.F. Factors Corporation), 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Jordache (Ditto Apparel), 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Jou and DCB Apparel, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- J.P. Hanger, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- J.P. Sporstwear, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- J.R. Le Yang Corporation, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Kamhi Fashion Group, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- K.G. Knitting Mills (Workers List Assessment ), 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- K.G. Knitting Mills, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Kicks Fashions INC., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- King Star Garment, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Norma Kamali, INC., 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- La Candilaria, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Knit Rite Company, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Knit Work Productions, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Kong Enterprises, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Labels for Less, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Liz Claiborne (Mt. Pocono), 1988-1994 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Lechters INC., 1993 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Leslie Fay Companies, INC., 1966-1995 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Linen Star, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Lynch Novelty, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- M and W Warehouse, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Maidenform INC., 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Maidenform INC., 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Majestic Shapes, 1987-1994 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Mandarin Knitting-El Salvador, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Merry Go Round Enterprises, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- New Balance, campaign materials, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Necessary Objects, files from 1st petition, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Necessary Objects, lawsuits, 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Necessary Objects, contractors, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Necessary Objects, contractors, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Necessary Objects, miscellany, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Necessary Objects, inside shop/workers/floor plan, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)